I heard the conversation. You want to go to the research facility.
我都聽說了 妳想去研究機構吧
You have all the more reason not to cause troubles.
那就更不應該惹事生非
What do you mean?
什麼意思
Before you start opposing your superior, you must act like an obedient soldier.
想反抗上級時 就必須先裝乖
Are you willing to help me get to Naomi?
妳願意幫我找直見囉
Certainly. After all, she is one of us.
那當然 畢竟我們也算是夥伴嘛
I'll gather information about the facility.
我幫妳收集關於研究機構的情報
For the time being, behave and carry out your mission.
所以現在先乖乖地執行任務吧
I found him.
找到了
Nagi is in the underground tunnel.
那歧 在地下道路
He's been brought onto a car. I don't know where they are headed.
被人移上車 不知道要去哪
If Nagi is really there,
如果他真的是那歧
if he's still alive,
他還活著的話
I must talk to him.
我想跟他聊聊
Nagi!
那歧
Wait, Nagi!
等等 那歧
Nagi...
那歧…
SCARLET NEXUS
《緋紅結繫》
♫A crime in reality♫
現實的Crimｅ
♫For Heaven's sake♫
For Heaven's sake
♫Accepts any fake♫
接受虛假
♫And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♫
永恆的幻想 層層逝去
♫Won't take it at all, I get sick♫
絕非完美 I get sick
♫A girl looking back♫
轉身而來的少女
♫Casts the miracle into the instant world♫
在這瞬息世界中 落下了奇蹟
♫Did you lie♫
Did you lie
♫Spit the venom♫
Spit the venom
♫I know why♫
I know why
♫I've found a game of ecstasy♫
找到了 絕頂的遊戲
♫Red Criminal gets life♫
Red Criminal gets life
♫I've never been in love♫
I've never been in love
♫Don’t know when I started getting sick of this world♫
我何時開始厭倦了這樣的世界
♫We will fly♫
We will fly
♫Someday I won't be crying♫
Someday I won't be crying
♫I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♫
為了不再傷害 而犧牲了自己
TRUTH HIDDEN IN THE HOSPITAL
(醫院的真相)
ALERT
(警報)
Great, we finally found you.
太好了 終於見到你了
I've been worried about you.
我一直很擔心你
It's all right now.
沒事了
Come with us.
跟我們一起回去吧
Nagi.
那歧
I can't go back.
回不去了…
I can't go back!
我回不去了
We just want to know what happened to you.
我們只想知道 你遇到了什麼事
No one will blame you.
沒有人會怪你的…
So you want to know...
你想知道…嗎…
But I have no idea either.
連我都無法理解
My mind went blank.
當時我的腦袋突然一陣麻
It was as though someone was stirring up my mind.
就像有人在攪亂我的腦
Nagi...
那歧…
Yuito, you must leave now.
結人 快逃 不能留在這裡
You must get out of this place now!
總之 我們盡快逃離此地
I'll buy you some time. Just run!
我來斷後 你們快逃
I'll fight by your side.
那我跟你一起戰鬥
No.
不可以
I don't even know when I'll turn on you and kill you!
我不知道何時會性格大變殺了你們
It's just like back then...
就像當時那樣
I don't care!
沒關係
I will stop you for sure!
這次我會阻止你的
You will become just like me!
你們會像我一樣…
No, they might turn you into Others!
不 搞不好會被變成怪異
Turned into Others?
被變成怪異
-Yuito, I'm sorry. -Nagi!
-結人 抱歉了 -那歧
Yuito, thank you.
結人 謝謝你
I'm sorry I can no longer be part of the team.
抱歉 不能跟你們一起行動
Sorry.
對不起
Luka, why did you do it?
魯卡 你為什麼
Because you weren't thinking straight.
因為你無法保持冷靜
Nagi was right.
那歧說的沒錯
We should leave this place at once.
我們必須盡快離開這裡
But...
可是
We now know about the government's secret.
我們已經知道政府的祕密了
It's too dangerous to stay here any longer.
繼續留在這裡會很危險
They are here.
來了
-They come in great number. -Yuito, run while you can.
-數量真多 -結人 快逃
He took out those monsters on his own.
一個人 就打倒大量的怪異
This is impressive.
太了不起了
It seems like the experiment went well.
看來實驗進行得很順利
Our effort was worth it after all.
費了我們不少功夫呢
Get to a shelter!
快去避難所
The Others were waiting to ambush us.
怪異好像故意潛伏在那裡
Is everyone all right?
各位 沒事吧
Major General Fubuki.
吹雪連隊長
No one was hurt.
我們都沒事
Good.
太好了
If you are contacting us,
吹雪主動聯絡我們
that means the government knows about our operation.
就表示我們的行動被政府掌握了
Yes.
是的
The government is discussing your punishments.
政府正在討論給你們的處分
So you knew all along
吹雪連隊長早就知道…
why Nagi was taken to that place?
那歧為何會被帶到那裡了嗎
I know.
知道
It was my responsibility that he was turned into that.
那歧會變成那樣 我也有責任
What do you mean?
這是什麼意思
That hospital
那間醫院
is used to brainwash anyone who would
是政府專門給不利於己的人…
go against the government.
洗腦之處
Nagi witnessed Naomi's metamorphosis.
那歧因目睹直見的怪異化
That was why he was taken there.
才會被帶到那裡的
You didn't get the same treatment because I took it upon myself to monitor you.
而你們 因我提出 由我來監視的條件 才得以倖免
But before that, Nagi was already taken there.
但在這之前 那歧就被他們逮到了
-I see. -Nagi was hurt and brought to a hospital.
-這樣啊 -當時那歧因受傷被帶到醫院
That was when they did it.
就是那個時候吧
Sorry.
抱歉…
I wish I could have found out sooner.
如果我能早點發覺就好了
This isn't your fault, Major General Fubuki.
這…這不是吹雪連隊長的錯
May I ask,
請問…
what do you mean about Naomi's metamorphosis?
直見的怪異化是什麼意思
Wasn't she killed in action?
她不是戰死了嗎
I see.
原來如此
Naomi didn't die a soldier but was turned into a monster.
直見沒有戰死 而是變成怪異了
Naomi was turned into Other?
直見變成怪異了
I'll start from the very beginning.
我從頭開始說明
But as a member of the Ichijo family, I hope you don't overreact.
但身為一條家的一份子 希望妳聽了別難過
Yes.
是…
That hospital
那間醫院
is the New Himuka government's research facility
是新日向政府的國家研究單位
to conduct brain power experiments.
進行著超腦力研究
They make adjustments to the brain to draw out greater power.
藉由調整大腦 引導出更強的超腦力
However, there are two side effects.
其結果 出現了兩種副作用
Rehabilitation, right?
人格矯正 對吧
Yes.
沒錯
The other side effect is metamorphosis.
另一個副作用則是怪異化
Contacting certain materials
藉由接觸特殊物質
will trigger the metamorphosis.
讓生物變成怪異
Any creature with a brain
只要是有腦的生物
will turn into Other.
都能變成怪異
Hold on.
請等一下
Do you mean the culprit that turned Naomi into a monster
你的意思是 把直見變成怪異的
was the government all along?
其實是政府嗎
Yes.
沒錯
People will start to suspect if this conversation went on any longer.
這些事說太久會遭人懷疑
I'll send you the next order.
我會再下達指令給你們
Before that, stand by.
在這之前先待機
Major General Fubuki,
請問 為何吹雪連隊長
why didn't the government do anything to you even when you know their secrets?
知道這麼多內幕 政府卻沒對你做什麼
It's simple.
原因很簡單
I'm siding with the system.
我是站在體制這邊的
I'm their lapdog.
也就是 政府的狗
Luka had learned a great deal from Karen.
魯卡也從卡連口中 聽過不少內幕
You could ask him.
有問題就問他吧
Luka, was everything Major General Fubuki told us
魯卡 吹雪連隊長所說的…
true?
是真的嗎
Yes, he was telling the truth.
是真的
It was a long time ago.
這是很久以前的事了
There was a woman by the name Alice.
有位名為愛麗絲一條的女性
Alice was the former hospital Chief's daughter.
愛麗絲 是怪伐軍醫院 前理事長的女兒
She was also the fiancee of Major General Fubuki from Spring Pharmaceuticals.
同時 也是詩賓製藥 吹雪連隊長的未婚妻
Auntie Alice.
愛麗絲姑姑…
If I remember correctly, she was scouted into the force.
我記得 她也是招募入隊的
But she was killed in action.
之後 因公殉職了
She...
她…
was turned into Other.
變成怪異了
Was it the government's doing?
她也是被政府…
No. I heard there was an accident during one of the operations.
不 聽說是在執行任務中 發生了意外
But still,
這樣的話…
how did she turn into Other?
人怎麼會 變成怪異呢
My brother and Fubuki started investigating.
所以 哥哥和吹雪 開始私下調查原因
During the process,
其過程中
they found out the government was conducting rehabilitation and metamorphosis experiment.
發現新日向政府進行了 人格矯正和怪異化研究
There was a surveillance system throughout all major cities.
以及對各個都市設置監視系統
If the project was conducted by the government,
既然是新日向政府帶領的研究計畫
did my father know too?
爸爸會不會也知道
I think he did.
我想他應該知道
It's best to assume all central executives know about the experiments.
最好做好所有中心要員 都知道的心理準備
So my brother knows too.
所以…哥哥也知道囉
Only I was kept in the dark.
只有我什麼都不清楚…
What is it, Major General Spring?
詩賓少將 有什麼事嗎
I was told your subordinates did something that would cause us trouble.
聽說你的部下 做了多餘的事
That's what I am here for.
關於這件事 我有話要說
Naomi is here.
直見 就在這裡…
Are you sure you want to join me?
你們 真的要跟著我嗎
I might get you into troubles.
可能會惹上麻煩喔
I am yours to command as long as I can be of service for you.
為了重 我願意隨妳使喚
-I am... -Come on, Kasane.
-我也是… -重 妳真是的
We are your friends. Have some trust in us.
我們是同伴 偶爾也多依賴我們點
-I... -We're throwing out lives away like lunatics.
-我… -唉 這麼快就不要命地違背政府
Why am I not surprised at all?
真像我們的作風
-I... -I will follow you as well.
-我… -我跟大家一樣
Using the information Arashi gathered,
而且我以嵐提供的情報為基礎
I've prepared the safest routes for you.
準備好了安全動線喔
Thank you, Haruka.
遙 謝謝妳
We're counting on you for navigation.
那就交給妳導航了
Huh?
咦
Shiden, aren't you coming with us?
紫電不跟來嗎
Let's get working.
快點走吧
This place is bleak.
真是沒氣氛的地方
It looks too spooky.
看起來就很詭異
We need a password.
好像需要密碼…
Haruka, can you bypass it?
遙 能想辦法嗎
Sorry, there is no useful data I can use.
抱歉 我沒找到能參考的情報
Don't worry. Everything has a flaw.
放心吧 百密終有一疏的
You actually unlocked it!
妳竟然解開了
Unbelievable. We didn't know you could do that.
真是的 妳何時準備好的
Seiran's security isn't something to write home about.
青藍的安全系統也不怎麼樣嘛
Isn't this an Other research facility?
這裡不是研究怪異的機構嗎
Why does it look like a factory?
怎麼看起來像座工廠
Not to mention the stench.
而且…這是什麼怪味道
It's unbearable.
難聞得不得了
What are they producing?
這裡到底在製作什麼
This is...
這是…
Do you know what these are?
妳知道這是什麼嗎
These ampoules
這些安瓿
are the same as the ampoule
跟直見怪異化時
a Seiran soldier dropped after turning Naomi.
青藍軍曾掉落的安瓿一樣
Furthermore...
而且…
I once saw these at my home when I was a child.
小時候…我曾在家裡 看過相同的東西
When we talk about the Randalls,
說到蘭德爾家族
Randall Industries comes to mind.
就會想到蘭德爾重工
Are they connected to the ampoules as well?
該不會跟這些安瓿有關吧
It's possible.
有可能
But I'm not sure either.
但 我也不清楚
There are too many uncertainties.
總之 有太多不確定因素了
Arashi, tell us before you act.
嵐 妳又擅自行動
The basics of spy operation
做諜報活動的基本功夫
are to acquire information in the shortest amount of time.
就是用最可靠的方法 迅速取得情報
Impressive, Arashi.
真不愧是嵐
The security system might as well be non-existent before you.
安全系統在妳面前 簡直就是裝飾品
I wouldn't want her as my enemy.
我最不想與這種人為敵
Indeed.
就是說嘛
She might dig up all the dirt from your past.
搞不好幾百年的黑歷史 都會被她挖出來喔
I can hear you.
我聽到了喔
Perhaps I should do you a favor and start digging up dirt on you.
我也能如你們所願 現在立刻挖出來
Arashi?
嵐
This is...
這是…
Everyone, run toward ten o'clock!
各位 往十點鐘方向逃
Let's go.
快走吧
What is this place?
這是什麼地方
Is this Alice's Wonderland?
愛麗絲夢遊仙境嗎
You're right. We look tiny in this place.
真的 我們簡直就像是變小了一樣
Sister...
姊姊…
I knew it, my sister is here.
姊姊果然在這裡
Sister, where are you?
姊姊 妳在哪
Sister!
姊姊
Kasane! I know you want to see her.
重 我理解妳的心情
But please calm down a little!
但請妳保持安靜
Kasane...
重…
This voice, it's my sister!
這個聲音…姊姊
Is that you?
是姊姊嗎
Kasane...
重…
Sister.
姊姊
It really is you.
果然是姊姊
Are you really Kasane?
真的是 重嗎…
If you can brain talk with Naomi...
能跟直見腦部對話了
She must be close.
那麼 她應該就在這附近
I've detected Naomi's presence. It's behind the door on the right.
我這裡也捕捉到 直見的反應 就在右邊後方的門裡
I'll be there at once.
我馬上過去
Kasane! Wait...
重 等等 我…
No, don't open it!
不行 別打開
Please, don't come any closer.
拜託…別過來
Kasane...
重…
Sister...
姊姊
This is the form she lives in now.
這…就是…直見現在的模樣
Is this Naomi?
這就是…直見
Sister, I'm sorry.
姊姊 對不起
You became this for saving me.
妳…是為了保護我才…
It's all right, Kasane.
重 沒關係
I'm glad I could save you.
能保護到重 就好了
But...
可是…
It's all right.
真的沒關係
I'm glad you're all right.
太好了 看到妳這麼有精神
I'm alive now because you saved me.
託姊姊的福 我現在很好
That's more than I can ask for.
那我就心滿意足了
I was worried about you.
不然 我真的很擔心…
Why were you worried about me?
為什麼是姊姊擔心我
I should be worried. I should have protected you!
明明是我要擔心姊姊 要保護妳才對啊
You are always too dense.
姊姊個性較笨拙
I must protect you.
所以我得保護妳
That was mean, Kasane.
重 妳好過分喔
But in the end...
可是 到最後…
Sorry, Sister...
姊姊 對不起…
Kasane, Naomi would be sad if you kept apologizing.
重 妳一直道歉 直見也會很難受的
Indeed.
就是啊
If you truly care about Naomi,
真為直見著想的話
this reunion is the best you can ask for for the time being.
兩人好不容易重逢的這個時刻 就別期望過多了
We have the location now.
反正我們也知道地點了
Captain Kyoka, I'm sorry.
鏡花隊長 對不起
I'm now this monstrosity...
我變成…這個模樣…
How are you?
沒關係 妳還好嗎
Are you hurt or ill?
有沒有生病或受傷
Did anyone here bully you?
這裡的人 沒對妳太粗魯吧
I'm doing well.
我很好
Even when I'm Other,
這裡的人 對變成怪異的我
people still treat me well.
仍然很親切…
Sister...
姊姊…
But after the ampoule's effect wears off,
不過 安瓿效力過後…
it becomes to painful.
我會…很痛苦…
I won't be able to communicate.
無法…溝通…
Kasane...
重…
Please,
拜託妳
do not come here again.
不要再來…這裡了…
Please forget about me.
求妳…忘了我吧
No way!
我不要
Sister, I've finally found you!
姊姊 我好不容易找到妳
I finally reunite with you!
好不容易見到面耶
The ampoule's effect is wearing off.
安瓿的效力…消失…
Kasane, I'm sorry.
重…對不起…
Please, leave this place.
拜託…出去…
Leave while you can!
快點 快
Kasane, if you care about Naomi,
重 妳為直見著想的話
you must leave now.
就快離開吧
Sister!
姊姊
Just as I expected, you came.
妳果然還是來了
I suspect we've been toyed by Major General Karen all this time.
我們幾個 該不會被卡連連隊長 玩弄在股掌之中吧
Naomi can retain her consciousness with the help of the ampoule.
直見只要有安瓿就能保有意識
But this is only a temporary solution.
但 這只是暫時的處理方式
Is there a way to make her normal again?
有方法讓直見恢復原狀吧
For that, I need your brain power.
為此 我需要妳的超腦力
My power?
我的
Before everything is ready, please be patient.
在我準備好一切之前 耐心等待
Naomi will be safe during this time.
這段期間 直見不會有生命危險
Keeping information from each other is a good way to bring distrust.
隱瞞過多的情報 會破壞彼此的信賴
Make yourself clear.
妳想說什麼
I have one question for you.
我只問一個問題
What was the material used to make
你給直見注射的安瓿
the ampoule you injected Naomi with?
是用什麼材料製作的
Good, you came back safely.
太好了 你們平安回來了
Major General Fubuki helped out.
託吹雪連隊長的福
Was he the one who persuaded Chief Sumeragi for us?
是連隊長幫我們說服皇本部長的吧
It took a great deal of effort.
好不容易呢
But if this happened again,
不過 再發生什麼事的話
it would be hard to appease him.
我也很難再說服本部長了
Be mindful of your actions.
所以請幾位務必注意
Yes.
是
Excuse me,
不好意思
this is from the OSF hospital.
這是怪伐軍醫院
They want Captain Yuito to have this.
要交給結人隊長的東西
It's for me?
給我的
We left the hospital before we got the medicine.
我們拿到藥前 就離開醫院了
So they sent it here instead.
所以他們特地送過來的吧
This is...
這是…
♫I don't need to let fate dictate me♫
無須被命運所指使
♫Because I believe that I can rewrite it♫
相信定會被改寫
♫I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♫
讓我們今後 繼續做著夢
♫Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♫
朝陽正光輝燦爛 隨後落下
♫What's waiting for us at the world's end♫
在世界的盡頭 究竟等著什麼
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going♫
未來 燈火永恆不滅
♫Who can shake us♫
誰在威脅我們
♫Who can define us♫
誰為我們決定
♫It's nothing less than our story♫
這是屬於我們的故事
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♫
未來 你心中的燈火永恆不滅
THE DUBIOUS AMPOULE
(可疑的特效藥)